<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IOT on wubigo</title>
    <link>https://wubigo.com/tags/iot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in IOT on wubigo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 13:40:38 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wubigo.com/tags/iot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect KEPServer to Ali IoT</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/connect-kepserver-to-ali-iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 13:40:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/connect-kepserver-to-ali-iot/</guid>
      <description>Configure an MQTT Client Agent within the IoT Gateway Plug-In for KEPServerEX
to send data to Ali IoT. The connection can be made using MQTT over Transmission
Control Protocol (TCP) and MQTT over Transport Layer Security (TLS).
set up Kepware KEPServerEX IoT Gateway on Windows to connect with the MQTT bridge
of IoT Core to push streaming data to Cloud and send control messages from IoT
Core back to KEPServerEX</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>物联网核心构件</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/iot-building-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 18:43:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/iot-building-blocks/</guid>
      <description> 物联网架构 An IoT Architecture consists of the following: - Peripherals, which we call “things”. - Sensors attached to these things to gauge and transmit their data and information. - Network connection through which data is transmitted (wireless or wired). - Remote Cloud to which data is transmitted by the system.
物联网核心构件 Sensors Microcontrollers Gateways Applications 物联网分层架构 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOT Notes</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/iot-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 18:20:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/iot-notes/</guid>
      <description>The dispersed nature of the Internet of Things (IoT) presents a major operational challenge that is uncommon in the traditional Internet or enterprise networks[5]. Devices that are managed together &amp;mdash; say a fleet of railcars &amp;mdash; are not physically colocated. Instead, they are widely geographically distributed. The operational approaches for management and security used in enterprise networks, where most hosts are densely contained in buildings or campuses, do not translate to the IoT.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>