<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BIGDATA on wubigo</title>
    <link>https://wubigo.com/tags/bigdata/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BIGDATA on wubigo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 13:40:38 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wubigo.com/tags/bigdata/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect KEPServer to Ali IoT</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/connect-kepserver-to-ali-iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 13:40:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/connect-kepserver-to-ali-iot/</guid>
      <description>Configure an MQTT Client Agent within the IoT Gateway Plug-In for KEPServerEX
to send data to Ali IoT. The connection can be made using MQTT over Transmission
Control Protocol (TCP) and MQTT over Transport Layer Security (TLS).
set up Kepware KEPServerEX IoT Gateway on Windows to connect with the MQTT bridge
of IoT Core to push streaming data to Cloud and send control messages from IoT
Core back to KEPServerEX</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Lake vs Warehouse</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/data-lake-vs-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 15:58:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/data-lake-vs-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>Data catalogs solve the problem by tagging fields and data sets with consistent business terms and providing a shopping-type interface that allows the users to find data sets by describing what they are looking for using the business terms that they are used to, and to understand the data in those data sets through tags and descriptions that use business terms.
Data lakes are the do-it-yourself version of a data warehouse, allowing data engineering teams to pick and choose the various metadata, storage, and compute technologies they want to use depending on the needs of their systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Scrapy</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/web-scrapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 08:57:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/web-scrapy/</guid>
      <description>用户代理 mobile devices browsing the web often see a pared-down ver‐ sion of sites, lacking banner ads, Flash, and other distractions. If you try changing your User-Agent to something like the following, you might find that sites get a little easier to scrape!
User-Agent:Mozilla/5.0 (iPhone; CPU iPhone OS 7_1_2 like Mac OS X) AppleWebKit/537.51.2 (KHTML, like Gecko) Version/7.0 Mobile/11D257 Safari/9537.53  scrapy architecture The data flow in Scrapy is controlled by the execution engine, and goes like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>大数据存储</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/project/sds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 16:45:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/project/sds/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flink Cluster</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/flink-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 17:08:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/flink-cluster/</guid>
      <description>execution environment Creates an execution environment that represents the context in which the program is currently executed. If the program is invoked standalone, this method returns a local execution environment. If the program is invoked from within the command line client to be submitted to a cluster, this method returns the execution environment of this cluster.  REST instead of akka in 1.5 changing the client to communicate via REST instead of akka.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>