<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NETWORK on 为人民服务</title>
    <link>https://wubigo.com/tags/network/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NETWORK on 为人民服务</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 16:18:43 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wubigo.com/tags/network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>K8S CNI</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/k8s-cni/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 16:18:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/k8s-cni/</guid>
      <description>CNI as the Kubernetes plugin model, There will be some unfortunate side-effects
Most of them are relatively minor (for example, docker inspect will not show an IP address), but some are significant. In particular, containers started by docker run might not be able to communicate with containers started by Kubernetes, and network integrators will have to provide CNI drivers if they want to fully integrate with Kubernetes
CNI was created as a minimal specification, built alongside a number of network vendor engineers to be a simple contract between the container runtime and network plugins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K8S网络基础</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/k8s-network-basic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 19:39:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/k8s-network-basic/</guid>
      <description>K8S网络基础
K8S简介 K8S是自动化部署和监控容器的容器编排和管理工具。各大云厂商和应用开发平台都提供基于K8S的容器服务。 如果觉得K8S托管服务不容易上手或者和本公司的业务场景不很匹配，现在也有很多工具帮助在自己的数据 中心或私有云平台搭建K8S运行环境。
 Minikube kops kubeadm  如果你想搭建一个测试环境，请参考
 从K8S源代码构建容器集群(支持最新稳定版V1.13.3) 一个脚步部署K8S  Kubernetes主要构件:
 主节点： 主要的功能包括管理工作节点集群，服务部署，服务发现，工作调度，负载均衡等。 工作节点： 应用负载执行单元。 服务规范： 无状态服务，有状态服务，守护进程服务，定时任务等。   K8S网络基础 K8S网络模型
 每一个POD拥有独立的IP地址 任何两个POD之间都可以互相通信且不通过NAT 集群每个节点上的代理(KUBELET)可以和该节点上的所有POD通信  K8S网络模型从网络端口分配的角度为容器建立一个干净的，向后兼容的规范，极大的方便和简化应用从虚拟机往容器迁移的流程。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cdn note</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/2014-04-03-cdn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 19:39:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/2014-04-03-cdn/</guid>
      <description>The main point of a Content Distribution Network (CDN) is to put the content as close to the end-user as possible, thereby reducing the Distance component of the Round Trip Time (RTT) and speeding up the request. Simply serving static content from a s# sub-domain for CDN.
The advantages of serving content from such a sub-domain, however, are that
The sub-domain can be a cookie-less domain
If you use your cookies correctly (ie.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>