<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IAAS on OS/APP HARDCORE</title>
    <link>https://wubigo.com/tags/iaas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in IAAS on OS/APP HARDCORE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 19:39:03 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wubigo.com/tags/iaas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>cdn note</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/2014-04-03-cdn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 19:39:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/2014-04-03-cdn/</guid>
      <description>The main point of a Content Distribution Network (CDN) is to put the content as close to the end-user as possible, thereby reducing the Distance component of the Round Trip Time (RTT) and speeding up the request. Simply serving static content from a s# sub-domain for CDN.
The advantages of serving content from such a sub-domain, however, are that
The sub-domain can be a cookie-less domain
If you use your cookies correctly (ie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>linux note</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/linux-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 19:39:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/linux-notes/</guid>
      <description>iptables规则配置  表与链   调用链顺序   检查内存 ram speed and type
 dmidecode  sudo dmidecode --type memory # dmidecode 3.0 Getting SMBIOS data from sysfs. SMBIOS 2.6 present. Handle 0x003E, DMI type 17, 28 bytes Memory Device Array Handle: 0x003C Error Information Handle: Not Provided Total Width: Unknown Data Width: Unknown Size: No Module Installed Form Factor: DIMM Set: 1 Locator: XMM1 Bank Locator: Not Specified Type: DDR3 Type Detail: Synchronous Speed: Unknown Manufacturer: JEDEC ID: Serial Number: Asset Tag: Not Specified Part Number: Rank: Unknown   lshw   sudo lshw -class memory memory:0 description: System Memory physical id: 3c slot: System board or motherboard *-bank:0 description: DIMM DDR3 Synchronous [empty] vendor: JEDEC ID: physical id: 0 slot: XMM1 *-bank:1 description: DIMM DDR3 Synchronous 1333 MHz (0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux File System Read Write Performance Test</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/2011-06-03-io-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 19:39:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/2011-06-03-io-performance/</guid>
      <description>dstat $dstat -d -nt $dstat -nt $dstat -N eth2,eth3  pkstat sudo apt-get install pktstat sudo pktstat -i eth0 -nt  nethogs sudo apt-get install nethogs sudo nethogs  EPEL http://www.cyberciti.biz/faq/fedora-sl-centos-redhat6-enable-epel-repo/
$ cd /tmp $ wget http://mirror-fpt-telecom.fpt.net/fedora/epel/6/i386/epel-release-6-8.noarch.rpm # rpm -ivh epel-release-6-8.noarch.rpm  How do I use EPEL repo?
Simply use the yum commands to search or install packages from EPEL repo:
# yum search nethogs # yum update # yum --disablerepo=&amp;quot;*&amp;quot; --enablerepo=&amp;quot;epel&amp;quot; install nethogs  System administrators responsible for handling Linux servers get confused at times when they are told to benchmark a file system&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hpcloud Notes</title>
      <link>https://wubigo.com/post/hpcloud-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 17:53:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wubigo.com/post/hpcloud-notes/</guid>
      <description> 惠普混合云 惠普tripleO整体方案 惠普混合云主要模块 网络控制节点 授权认证部分源代码 医疗数据分析  医疗数据某业务流程  医疗数据处理图  医疗项目部分工作内容
  部分任务 部分任务 部分源代码 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>